export const pmQuestions = [ 
    {
      question: "1. What is the first step in a park development project?",
      answers: [
        "Landuse Planning",
        "Environmental Impact Assessment",
        "Design",
        "Funding",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "Landuse Planning",
      category : "Project Management"
    },
    {
      question: "2. What is the first step that a park development manager take decide if the project requires Environmental Impact Assessment?",
      answers: [
        "Check with the Park Planning team",
        "Consult the nature groups",
        "Email National Biodiversity Centre",
        "Refer to Enviromental Impact Assessment Framework and submit Form A",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "Refer to Enviromental Impact Assessment Framework and submit Form A",
      category : "Project Management"
    },
    {
      question: "3. What conditions does a park development manager NOT decide when deciding on method of contracting method to develop a park? ",
      answers: [
        "Project timeline",
        "Funding",
        "Public Feedback",
        "None of the above"
      ],
      correctAnswer:"None of the above",
      category : "Project Management"
    },
    {
    question: " Who signs off the project brief?",
    answers:[
      "CEO",
      "Cluster Head",
      "Park Planning",
      "Director level of the operations team taking over",
    ],
     correctAnswer: "Director level of the operations team taking over",
     category : "Contract Management"
    },
    {
      question: " When can term contract civil works be used for park development?",
      answers:[
        "When cost of development works is more than $1,000,000",
        "When there are many star rate items as part of the development work",
        "When cost of development works is less than $500,000 and works are in the price schedule of rates",
        "When the funding timeline is tight",
    ],
       correctAnswer: "When cost of development works is less than $500,000 and works are in the price schedule of rates",
       category : "Contract Management"
      },
      {
        question: " According to PSCCOC, what is the contractor's responsibility when applying for an Extension of Time (EOT)?",
        answers:[
        "To submit a written application only after the project completion date",
        "To provide evidence of the delay and its impact on the project timeline",
        "To automatically receive the EOT as soon as an application is submitted",
        "To submit an EOT request only if instructed by the Engineer or Project Manager",
        ],
        correctAnswer: "To provide evidence of the delay and its impact on the project timeline",
        category : "Contract Management"
      },
      {
        question: "  Which of the following native tree species is commonly chosen in Singapore’s park development for its low maintenance requirements?",
        answers:[
        "Tembusu (Fagraea fragrans)",
        "Rain Tree (Samanea saman)",
        "African Mahogany (Khaya senegalensis)",
        "Angsana (Pterocarpus indicus)",
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Tembusu (Fagraea fragrans)",
        category : "Horticulture"
    },
      {
        question: "What is one of the main benefits of planting native trees in Singapore's urban landscapes?",
        answers:[
          "Native trees require more frequent watering than non-native species",
          "They enhance biodiversity by providing food and habitat for local wildlife",
          "Native trees grow faster and require less pruning than imported trees",
          "They improve soil quality for agricultural crop planting",
        ],
         correctAnswer: "They enhance biodiversity by providing food and habitat for local wildlife",
         category : "Horticulture"
        },
        {
          question: "In Singapore's park development, how does horticulture contribute to sustainable urban planning?",
          answers:[
            "By introducing foreign plant species that require more water",
            "By using native and adaptive plants that reduce maintenance and water needs",
            "By focusing on monoculture planting for consistent landscaping",
            "By planting exclusively ornamental species for aesthetic purposes",
          ],
           correctAnswer: "By using native and adaptive plants that reduce maintenance and water needs",
           category : "Horticulture"
          },

          {
            question: "Which of the following native tree species is commonly chosen in Singapore’s park development for its low maintenance requirements?",
            answers:[
            "Tembusu (Fagraea fragrans)",
            "Rain Tree (Samanea saman)",
            "African Mahogany (Khaya senegalensis)",
            "Angsana (Pterocarpus indicus)",
            ],
            correctAnswer: "Tembusu (Fagraea fragrans)",
            category : "Park Design"
          },
          {
            question: "What is one of the main benefits of planting native trees in Singapore's urban landscapes?",
            answers:[
              "Native trees require more frequent watering than non-native species",
              "They enhance biodiversity by providing food and habitat for local wildlife",
              "Native trees grow faster and require less pruning than imported trees",
              "They improve soil quality for agricultural crop planting",
            ],
             correctAnswer: "They enhance biodiversity by providing food and habitat for local wildlife",
             category : "Park Design"
            },
            {
              question: "In Singapore's park development, how does horticulture contribute to sustainable urban planning?",
              answers:[
                "By introducing foreign plant species that require more water",
                "By using native and adaptive plants that reduce maintenance and water needs",
                "By focusing on monoculture planting for consistent landscaping",
                "By planting exclusively ornamental species for aesthetic purposes",
              ],
               correctAnswer: "By using native and adaptive plants that reduce maintenance and water needs",
               category : "Park Design"
              },
  
    ]